[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In photography and cinematography, this type of light, sometimes called hair or shoulder light, provides separation between the subject and its background.", "correct_answer": "Back Light", "incorrect_answers": ["Motivated light", "Practical light", "Key light"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Prunus genus, to which peaches belong, does not includes which one of these trees?", "correct_answer": "Apple", "incorrect_answers": ["Almond", "Cherry", "Plum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What album was released by the rock band Weezer in 2001?", "correct_answer": "The Green Album", "incorrect_answers": ["Greenage", "Rock it Green", "Greenation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What sign flew over the school of Aristotle?", "correct_answer": "Let no one unfamiliar with geometry enter", "incorrect_answers": ["Know Thyself", "Es Will De garnish helfen", "All for Knowledge"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what geographical area is the Rock monitor lizard, or Legavaan, found?", "correct_answer": "Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["South America", "New Guinea", "Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who leads the attack on the gypsy camp in the movie, From Russia With Love?", "correct_answer": "Krilencu", "incorrect_answers": ["Morzeny", "Blofeld", "Rosa Klebb"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Eiffel 65 is a trio of Italian musicians who play electronic music. One of their biggest hits is Blue (Da Ba Dee). The album featured this hit.", "correct_answer": "Europop", "incorrect_answers": ["Eiffel 65", "Contact!", "Suggested Title - Crash Test"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do wolves mark their territory?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["By urinating", "By defecating", "By rubbing against objects"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the title of the oldest existing full length animated movie?", "correct_answer": "The Adventures of Prince Achmed", "incorrect_answers": ["The Beautiful Lukanida", "Pseudolpolis", "Peludopolis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An albatross can fly all day without flapping its wings.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term stands for the excessive fear of snakes?", "correct_answer": "Ophidiophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Arachnophobia", "Agoraphobia", "Novercaphobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1565, this German-Swiss naturalist became the first person to document and describe the pencil.", "correct_answer": "Conrad Gesner", "incorrect_answers": ["Edward  Naime", "William Munroe", "Nicolas Conte"]}]